<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<demos><!--此文件是自动生成的，请不要修改-->
   <name>Bar3D</name>
   <type>toolbox</type>
   <icon>HelpIcon.DEMOS</icon>
   <website/>
   <description>BAR3D   3-D bar plot.

BAR3D(X,Y,Z) plots the 3d bars defined by X, Y and Z, where X and
Y are m by n matrices which can be generated by meshgrid from vectors,
and Z is an m by n by p matrix. If p is greater than 1, p sets of m by
n bars are drawn in the same axes, the default arrangement of bars in
the same position but from different sets is being grouped along the
x axis, and this default behavior can be modified by setting the
parameter 'Arrange'.

BAR3D(X,Y,Z,C) additionally specifies the color of bars, where C is of
the same size as X or Y.

BAR3D(Z) is similar to BAR3D(X,Y,Z) but uses the column and row
indices of the elements in Z as x and y coordinates.

BAR3D(Z,C) additionally specifies the color of bars.

BAR3D(...,'Width',width) sets the value of the width of bars.

BAR3D(...,'Base',base) sets the base value of the plot, where base
can be a scalar value or an m by n matrix.

BAR3D(...,'Arrange',arrange) sets the arrangement of bars if Z is
a multidimensional matrix. Available options are 'hold', where bars
are plot in the same position, 'x', where bars are grouped along x
axis, 'y', where bars are grouped along y axis and 'z' where bars are
grouped along z axis or, in other words, stacked together.

BAR3D(...,'Gap',gap) sets the gap of bars if the arrangement is
'x' or 'y', where the gap is considered as a ratio, or 'z', where the
gap is considered as a numeric value.

BAR3D(...,'PropertyName',PropertyValue,...) sets the value of the
specified BAR3D property, apart from 'Width', 'Base', 'Arrange' and
'Gap'. The property names and values are the same as those of SURF.

BAR3D(AX,...) plots into AX instead of GCA.

h = BAR3D returns a handle to a surface plot object or multiple
handles to all the surface plot objects.

AXIS, CAXIS, COLORMAP, HOLD, SHADING and VIEW set figure, axes, and
surface properties which affect the display of the 3d bars.

Ze-Zheng Wu 10-1-21</description>
   <demosection>
      <label>bar3d</label>
      <demoitem>
         <label>example</label>
         <type>other</type>
         <source>example</source>
         <file>html/example.html</file>
      </demoitem>
   </demosection>
</demos>